Shigemura, Shigemura, Shigemura, Shigemura
Oh, my God.
I don't know.
Oh, Asuna, I've turned into
the biggest crybaby, haven't I?
The feeling is rising,
It's a true promise to me.
A miracle that I want,
It's the end of the series!
It's not our end.
I'll be there.
We're not going to see the future.
I can't see the future.
We can't see the future.
We're not going to see the future.
I'm going to see the future!
But I'm still asking.
I'm singing.
Ah, I'm going to spread
my eyes in the future!
I'm going to spread
my eyes
in
the future.
I'm off to practice.
I'll see you later, okay?
Good morning.
Good morning, Sugu.
Good morning!
God, seriously?
Instead of lurking, you
should have said something.
Yeah, well, you were practicing
and I didn't want to bother you.
I wasn't really practicing.
I guess it's just habit is all.
Oh.
At least you've been keeping it up.
It's light.
What?
It's not light.
It's timber bamboo.
Oh, yeah, right.
I meant, like, it's
lighter than I thought.
It's not as heavy as what I'm used to.
What the heck's he comparing it to?
Hey, you think maybe
we could give it a go?
What, you mean a match?
Like, seriously?
Yep.
A real match with pads and stuff.
Mmm, yeah, on second thought, no contact.
I mean, I'd feel like crap
if I ended up hurting you.
I still gotta dig out Grandpa's old gear.
How about we spar in the dojo?
Whoa, you sound pretty darn confident for
someone who's been asleep for two years.
For your information, I was a quarter-finalist
in the Middle School Nationals.
Seriously, though, are you
sure you're feeling up to this?
You might want to take it easy.
I've been doing rehab in the gym every
day, so I think I'm gonna be good to go.
What kind of stance is
that supposed to be?
Don't you worry about it.
This is my own style.
Okay. Ready? Uh-huh.
His head's wide open.
That'll be my first strike.
Huh?
It's an odd stance, but he looks composed.
Okay, then.
Oh my god, are you okay?
Okay, okay, you win.
You sure are strong, Sugu.
You'd mop the floor with Heathcliff.
Maybe you should sit down
or something. I'm good.
Thanks for the match.
Huh?
Did I hit you too hard? No, I'm okay.
Just years of habit.
Let's see, my footwork was
okay, but the attacks sucked.
I guess I can't use the sword skills I
acquired unless I got the system helping.
I have to say, I'm really surprised.
I mean, how long have you been
practicing behind my back?
Oh, you know, it is kind of fun after all.
But you never know, maybe
I'll take it up again. Really?
Oh, seriously? Yeah, sure.
You want to be my teacher?
Are you kidding?
Of course.
We'll train together like we used to.
After I build up some more muscle, okay?
I've been practicing, too.
Want to know what? Huh?
Nope, I'll keep it a secret.
That is so not cool.
You going anywhere today? Oh.
I don't know.
I guess...
the hospital?
Oh, you are. That's nice.
Her name's Asuna, right?
You visit her a lot.
Uh-huh.
As much as I can.
It's the only thing I can do for her.
Anyway, Sugu, it's my turn
to make breakfast today.
It'll be ready by the time
you finish your shower.
Okay.
It's been two months
since I beat Heathcliff,
two months since I beat the Death Game.
When I woke up, I talked to someone
from the Ministry of Internal Affairs.
I told them everything I knew about SAO,
and in exchange, they
told me where Asuna was.
I found out she was nearby in Saitama.
Asuna's family admitted her
to Tokoazawa General Hospital.
I also found out that besides her,
there's about 300 other players
who haven't woken up yet.
Akihiko Kayaba's still missing,
and people think he's keeping the players
in their comas as part of his plan.
SAO isn't over, not by a long shot.
Asuna.
Kazuto.
Sorry, I didn't know you were here.
Thank you for coming.
Hello, Mr. Yuki.
I hope it's okay I'm here.
Please, you can visit whenever you like.
I know it makes her happy.
Sir.
Oh, I don't think the
two of you have ever met.
This is Sugo.
He's our company's director of R &D.
I'm Nobuyuki Sugo.
It's a pleasure.
I'm Kazuto Kirigaya.
You're THE Kirito?
You're a hero. It's an honor.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I know we're not supposed to talk about
what happened inside the SAO server.
But he's my partner's son, so it's fine.
Besides, I've always thought
of him as part of my family.
Actually, sir, speaking of family,
if I may, I'd like to make it
official as soon as possible.
This is sudden.
Are you sure this is really what you want?
I mean, you're still young.
You have your whole life ahead of you.
Thank you for your concern,
but my heart's set on it.
It sounds strange, but even though
she's like this, she's still beautiful.
I'd like to see her in that wedding dress!
You have a point.
The sooner we prepare ourselves
for the inevitable, the better.
Sorry to cut the conversation short.
I have a meeting to get to.
We can talk more about this later.
Kazuto, take care.
I heard you and Asuna
were lovers in the game.
Is that true?
Uh-huh.
That is unfortunate.
It's going to make for one complicated
relationship between you and I.
In case you're curious, her father and
I were discussing her marriage to me.
No way.
You can't do that.
You have a point.
It's true, we can't legally marry.
But if the Yuki family adopts me, it'll
be as if we are, on paper that is.
Just like we're married.
The truth is, she's always hated
me, ever since we were kids.
Neither my parents nor hers know that.
If I proposed and she could speak, I'm
pretty sure her answer would be no.
For me, this situation is very favorable.
Stop it!
Who do you think you are?
You can't take advantage
of Asuna like this.
Take advantage?
Oh, please.
If anything, I have a right to her.
Perhaps I should explain why.
Any idea what happened to Argus?
They're the company that developed SAO.
I heard they closed it down. Very good.
The lawsuits and damages they
had to pay took their toll.
The company was forced into bankruptcy.
But the maintenance of the SAO
servers was given to another company.
An electronics manufacturer where
Asuna's father, Shozo Yuki, is the CEO.
Wrecked progress.
And I work for the company's
full-dive technology R &D division.
In other words, and without
getting into specifics,
you could say I'm the
one keeping Asuna alive.
Now I ask you, is it wrong for me to expect
a little compensation for my trouble?
I don't know what kind of promises
you made to each other in the game,
and I don't really care.
But I don't ever want to see
you here again! Understood?
And from now on, stay
away from the Yuki family.
We're having the ceremony here
on January 26th, a week from now!
Save the date.
Even though you're not welcome here
anymore, you should come to the wedding.
No need to thank me.
Well, Mr.
Hero
You've got the room all to yourself now.
Say goodbye and get out.
Kazuto!
The bathroom's all yours!
Jeez, what's wrong?
Why didn't you say something?
And turn on the heat,
it's freezing in here!
Sorry I just want to be left alone.
Hey how come you didn't
turn the heater on?
What's wrong are you okay?
Yeah it's nothing.
Okay but you're freezing
you're gonna catch a cold.
I could run you a hot bath if you want.
I'm so hopeless and weak
I didn't want you to see
this I swore no matter
what you'd never see me.
Being such a crybaby
is it Asuna is
she okay did something happen to her?
She's leaving.
Somewhere far away.
And I'll never.
I'm never gonna see her again.
Hey?
Hey, hang in there, okay?
If you really love someone that
much, even when things look hopeless,
you can't give up.
I know I can't.
And I won't lie to myself anymore.
Gosh, I remember it like it was yesterday.
Kazuto stood there looking at me,
and then he told me he wanted to
know who his real parents were.
I was so shocked, I
didn't know what to say.
He was only ten, but here's the thing.
Somehow, he logged onto the Citizen's
Registration Network and found the file.
That figures.
Sounds just like something he'd do.
I was so stunned, I couldn't
think of a way to deny it.
So what do I do instead?
I tell him how my big sister and
her husband are his real parents.
Wow.
Mom, I was wondering. About what?
I guess about the way he's
been since middle school.
He'd go into his room and
play games online for hours.
You think it's because he found
out about his real parents?
No, not at all.
He was always into
computers and technology.
By the time he was six, he'd already
built his own computer out of spare parts.
If anything, he's like that because
he's a huge computer nerd like me.
Or so he thinks.
Well, I'm heading home
and get dinner ready.
Don't stay too long, okay, Suguha?
Don't worry. I won't.
Happy birthday, kiddo.
He's my cousin.
Not my big brother.
I still have a hard time. Believing it.
My big brother.
But, in the end, your heart.
In the end, your heart.
Belongs to her.
Come on!
Wake up, Sugu!
It's morning.
I said you got to wake up now.
You're not going to have time to
practice if you don't wake up.
Oh, hey. Morning.
Rise and shine.
Hiya, Sleepy.
Um, I...
Oh, my God!
As weird as ever.
Just hang in there, okay?
She's right.
Yeah, she's right.
What the hell?
Asuna...
Next time, Land of the Fairies.